<?xml version="1.0"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.00</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to dissemminate information to anyone interested in their software products.  To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>OptiCode - Dr. Martin Sander Software Dev.</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>Steinachstr. 9A</Address_1>
        <Address_2 />
        <City_Town>Schriesheim</City_Town>
        <State_Province />
        <Zip_Postal_Code>D-69198</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>Germany</Country>
        <ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
        <ASP_Member_Number />
        <ESC_Member>N</ESC_Member>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.optivec.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Martin</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Sander</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>msander@optivec.com</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Martin</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Sander</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>info@optivec.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>sales@optivec.com</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>support@optivec.com</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>info@optivec.com</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone />
        <Support_Phone />
        <General_Phone />
        <Fax_Phone>+49-6203-925396</Fax_Phone>
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>CMATH for Borland C++ (DOS)</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>4.0</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>05</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>18</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2004</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>60</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Freeware</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win 3.1x</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
        <Program_System_Requirements>Borland C/C++ 4.0 or higher</Program_System_Requirements>
        <Program_Categories>programming, C, C++, libraries, math, science, engineering</Program_Categories>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>cbc400d.zip</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous>cbc334d.zip</Filename_Previous>
        <Filename_Generic>cmathdos.zip</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>cmathdos.zip</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>241599</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>241</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>0.2</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>N</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count />
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>N</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>complex,  math, library, cartesian, polar, number, programming</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Fast complex math library for BC++ (DOS)</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>CMATH: Complex math library (cartesian and polar) for Borland C/C++ (DOS)</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>CMATH for Borland C++ (DOS) makes fast complex-number math functions (cartesian and polar) available in three precisions. This comprehensive library was written in Assembler for superior speed and accuracy. All functions may be called from C or C++.</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>CMATH is a comprehensive library for complex-number arithmetics and 
mathematics, both in cartesian and polar format (float, double, and extended precision). The implementation in Assembler ensures superior speed, accuracy, and safety, as compared to other available complex class libraries with their inline or compiled C++ code. All CMATH functions may be called from C or C++. For Borland C++ 3.0 or higher.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>CMATH is a comprehensive library for complex-number arithmetics and 
mathematics, both in cartesian and polar format (float, double, and extended precision). The implementation in Assembly language ensures superior speed, accuracy, and safety, as compared to other available complex class libraries with their inline or compiled C++ code.  
All CMATH functions may be called either from C with type-specific function names (e.g., cf_sin, cd_exp, pf_sqrt) or from C++ with overloaded function names (sin, exp, sqrt, etc.). They are optimized for Pentium/PentiumXX, but will run on computers down to 386+387. This version is for Borland C/C++ 4.0 or higher (model DOS-LARGE).</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
<German>
        <Keywords>komplex, complex, mathematisch, Bibliothek, cartesisch, Polar, Koordinaten, Zahl, Funktion, Programmierung</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>Bibliothek fuer komplexe Mathematik fuer BC++</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>CMATH: Bibliothek fuer komplexe Mathematik (cartesische und Polar-Koordinaten) fuer Borland C/C++ (DOS)</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>CMATH ist eine umfassende Bibliothek fuer komplexe Mathematik, sowohl in cartesischen als auch in Polar-Koordinaten. Durch die Implementierung in Assembler werden hoechste Geschwindigkeit und Genauigkeit erreicht. Fuer das Speichermodell DOS-LARGE von Borland C++ 3.0+.</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>CMATH ist eine umfassende Bibliothek fuer komplexe Mathematik, sowohl in cartesischen als auch in Polar-Koordinaten (float-, double- und extended-genau). Durch die Implementierung in Assembler werden hoechste Geschwindigkeit, Genauigkeit und Sicherheit erreicht, die compiliertem C/C++-Quellcode weit ueberlegen sind.  Alle Funktionen koennen sowohl von C als auch von C++ aus aufgerufen werden. Fuer das Speichermodell DOS-LARGE von Borland C++ 3.0+.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>CMATH ist eine umfassende Bibliothek fuer komplexe Mathematik, sowohl in cartesischen als auch in Polar-Koordinaten (float-, double- und extended-genau). Durch die Implementierung in Assembler werden hoechste und compiliertem C/C++-Quellcode weit ueberlegene Geschwindigkeit, Genauigkeit und Sicherheit erreicht.  Alle Funktionen koennen entweder mit typenspezifischen Funktionsnamen von C aus aufgerufen werden (z.B. cf_sin, cd_exp, pf_sqrt) oder mit ueberladenen Funktionsnamen von C++ aus (z.B. sin, exp, sqrt). Die Shareware-Version ist fuer Pentium II-IV optimiert unter Wahrung von Rueckwaerts-Kompatibilitaet bis 386+387. Fuer das Speichermodell DOS-LARGE von Borland C/C++ 4.0+.</Char_Desc_2000>
</German>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://www.optivec.com/cmfuncs</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://www.optivec.com/order</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL />
        <Application_Icon_URL />
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://www.optivec.com/download/CMATHDOS.XML</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://www.optivec.com/download/CMATHDOS.ZIP</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>This product may be distributed through CD compilations or Shareware sites on the Internet, provided that you notify us by email about this.</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>This is the Freeware version of CMATH for DOS ("SOFTWARE"). 
It may be used under the following licence terms:   

1. This product is Freeware in the sense that you may use it free of charge for as long as you like for personal and/or educational purposes.   
2. Applications, created with the Freeware version of this SOFTWARE, may not be distributed to others or used for any commercial purpose.   
3. If you want to distribute programs containing functions of this SOFTWARE, you have to purchase the commercial registered version.   
4. This SOFTWARE is provided on an "as is" basis. Any explicit or implicit warranties for the SOFTWARE are excluded.   
5. Despite thorough testing of the SOFTWARE, errors and bugs cannot be excluded  with certainty. No claims as to merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose are made.   
6. You may not use the SOFTWARE in any environment or situation where personal injury or excessive damage to anyone's property (including your own) could arise from malfunctioning of the SOFTWARE.  
7. You may not decompile, disassemble, or otherwise reverse engineer the SOFTWARE into a machine-readable form. You may, however, inspect the functions it contains by means of debuggers like those included in the Borland and Microsoft compilers.  
Copyright for the SOFTWARE and its documentation:  
 (C) 1996-2004 OptiCode - Dr. Martin Sander Software Dev.  
All rights reserved.</EULA>
</Permissions>
<Simtel>
    <Simtel_Email />
    <Simtel_FORM>Y</Simtel_FORM>
    <Simtel_DOS_Category>Programming - turbo_c Borland Turbo C Programming Language</Simtel_DOS_Category>
    <Simtel_Platform>Select - Other Platform (blank)</Simtel_Platform>
    <Simtel_Category>Select - Category (blank)</Simtel_Category>
    <SIMTEL_FORM_VER>1.2 5/22/2002</SIMTEL_FORM_VER>
</Simtel>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
